

bethdixondesign@gmail.com

## **Experience**

Home Office, Interaction Design Intern

September 2017 - Current

I have designed on internal and external services through different stages of discovery, alpha, beta to live services. I helped to identify problem areas through researching with users and identifying key user needs. I have worked in delivery teams using agile methods to iterate designs and deliver quickly.

### Cramlington Kids Club, Interaction designer July 2017 - Current

I have researched and reviewed the existing website to look at existing usability, accessibility and content issues. I interviewed and researched with users to look at core uses of the website and to help structure and prioritise content upfront. I restructure the architecture by reviewing the content and cutting out pages that weren't used. I used a range of prototypes varying from basic sketches to mid fidelity prototypes. By putting something in front of the user's up front I was able to get quick feedback and make quick changes.

### Mentor Match, Interaction designer

September 2017 - June 2018

My role as a designer was to use insights from research to prioritise main design changes on the website. We were asked by a charity to redesign their website whilst focusing on creating a positive user experience and improving the accessibility and usability of the site. The team experimented using different research and design methods to test with users in an iterative process. We adhered to agile methods and worked in an iterative way to provide a working product that we could take out to users and present back findings to key stakeholders.

## Made of Steel, Graphic design

June 2018 - August 2018

I created a brand guidelines for a local fitness business that were going to be used on both digital and physical prints. I researched into existing local brands and created a design document that mapped out the main key elements of the brand.

## **Education**

#### **BSC Chartered Instituition**

Agile practicioner certificate June 2018 - London, UK

#### Northumbria University

1:1 Class BA Hons, Interactive Media Design September 2014 - July 2017 - Newcastle, UK

## The Blyth Academy

Computing, ICT & Product Design (Graded B-D) September 2012 – 2014 – Northumberland, UK

#### Bede Academy

10 GCSE'S (Graded A-D) September 2010 – 2012 – Northumberland, UK

#### About me

I am passionate about creating intuitive experiences for users by understanding core user needs and creating accessible services. I am motivated and like to make the best of challenging situations, and try to bring out the best in those around me.

# Skills: Design

Interaction design Prototyping Usability testing Personas Wireframing Sketching Storyboarding Mapping information architecture